Inventory of the Edwin Meese papers, 1941-1991
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speeches and Writings, 1981-1988 (Boxes 1-37)
  - Statement, Senate Judiciary Committee, Washington, D.C., 1987 March 4 (Box 25)
  - Statement on Authorization Legislation for the Department of Justice, Committee on the Judiciary, United States House of Representatives, Washington, D.C., 1987 March 5 (Box 25)
  - Speech, Center for the Study of the Presidency, Washington, D.C., 1987 March 7 (Box 25)
  - Remarks, University of Illinois Bicentennial Conference, Campaign, Illinois, 1987 March 7 (Box 25)
  - Address, National Association of General Contractors, Sheraton Washington Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1987 March 9 (Box 25)
  - Statement, United States House of Representatives Appropriations Subcommittee, Washington, D.C., 1987 March 10 (Box 25)
  - Remarks, National Parent's Resource Institute for Drug Education (PRIDE) Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, 1987 March 19 (Box 25)
  - Hartman Memorial Lecture, University of Mississippi, Oxford, Mississippi, 1987 March 19 (Box 25)
  - Remarks, Fairfax County Chamber of Commerce 9th Annual Valor Awards Ceremony, Springfield Hilton Hotel, Springfield, Virginia, 1987 March 20 (Box 26)
  - Address, Center for the Study of the Presidency 18th Annual Student Symposium, Hyatt Regency Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1987 March 21 (Box 26)
  - Brief remarks, D.C. National Guard 35th Annual Awards and Decorations Ceremony, D.C. Armory, Washington, D.C., 1987 March 22 (Box 26)
  - Address, Voice of America Workshop, HHS north building, Washington, D.C., 1987 March 23 (Box 26)
  - Speech, American Business Conference, Washington, D.C., 1987 March 25 (Box 26)
  - Press conference on tort reform, Department of Justice, Washington, D.C., 1987 March 26 (Box 26)
  - Address, New Mexico Council on Crime and Delinquency, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1987 March 27 (Box 26)
  - Speech, American Society for Public Administration, Boston, Massachusetts, 1987 March 31 (Box 26)
  - Address, Union League of Philadelphia Luncheon, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1987 April 3 (Box 26)
  - Speech, Philadelphia Society Bicentennial Luncheon, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1987 April 4 (Box 26)
  - Remarks, American Bar Association Criminal Justice System, San Francisco, California, 1987 April 9 (Box 26)
  - Address, Brookings Institution Seminar, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1987 April 12 (Box 26)
  - Speech, National Law Enforcement Council Lunch, Capitol Hill Club, Washington, D.C., 1987 April 13 (Box 26)
  - Forrestal Lecture, United States Naval Academy, Annapolis, Maryland, 1987 April 15 (Box 26)
  - Address, Daughters of the American Revolution, Capital Hilton Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1987 April 20 (Box 26)
  - Speech, Fifth Judicial Circuit 44th Annual Conference, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1987 April 21 (Box 26)
  - Remarks, SAC Conference (Federal Bureau of Investigation - Drug Enforcement Agency), Phoenix, Arizona, 1987 April 22 (Box 26)
  - Address, American Chamber of Commerce in Belgium, Palace Hotel, Brussels, Belgium, 1987 April 28 (Box 26)
  - "Rule of Law Must Cover Battle vs. Terrorism," speech, 1987 April 28 (Box 26)
  - Address, Kiwanis Club of Washington, D.C., Washington, D.C., 1987 April 30 (Box 26)
  - Remarks, White House Fellows Alumni Association, Washington, D.C., 1987 April 30 (Box 26)
  - Interview on Constitution with Steven Bell, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1987 May 1 (Box 27)
  - Remarks, Magna Carta Foundation of Philadelphia Law Day Ceremony and Luncheon, Independence Hall Courtyard, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1987 May 1 (Box 27)
  - Address, Federal Bar Association Special Bicentennial of the Constitution Meeting Sheraton Society Hill Hotel, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1987 May 1 (Box 27)
  - Speech, Liberty University 14th Commencement, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1987 May 4 (Box 27)
  - Remarks, University of San Diego Corporate Associates Recognition Luncheon, University Center, University of San Diego, Alcala Park, San Diego, California, 1987 May 6 (Box 27)
  - Address, Law Enforcement Intelligence Unit Conference, San Diego, California, 1987 May 6 (Box 27)
  - Comments, 1985 Legislative Conference of the National District Attorneys Association, Sheraton Crystal City Hotel, Arlington, Virginia, 1987 May 7 (Box 27)
  - Speech, 14th Annual Valley Prayer Breakfast, Woodland Hills, Los Angeles, California, 1987 May 7 (Box 27)
  - Address, St. Louis Clergy for Life Group, St. Louis, Missouri, 1987 May 8 (Box 27)
  - "Celebrate Your Constitution," speech, Palm Beach County Bar Association, West Palm Beach, Florida, 1987 May 11 (Box 27)
  - Speech, Organized Crime Drug Enforcement Task Force Conference, Adam's Mark Hotel, St. Louis, Missouri, 1987 May 13 (Box 27)
  - Testimony re: Coordination of National Drug Policy and Strategy, United States Senate Committee on the Judiciary, Washington, D.C., 1987 May 14 (Box 27)
  - Remarks, National Law Enforcement Officers' Memorial Check Presentation Ceremony, White House, Washington, D.C., 1987 May 14 (Box 27)
  - Speech, National District Attorneys' Association, Washington, D.C., 1987 May 18 (Box 27)
  - Remarks, Newspaper Carriers Association, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1987 May 19 (Box 27)
  - Speech, Chamber of Commerce, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1987 May 19 (Box 27)
  - Address, United States Marshals Conference, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1987 May 19 (Box 27)
  - Remarks, "Constitutional Roots, Right and Responsibilities," Smithsonian Institution Symposium, departmental auditorium, Washington, D.C., 1987 May 20 (Box 27)
  - Remarks, Smithsonian Institution Conference, Washington, D.C., 1987 May 20 (Box 27)
  - Speech on receiving Government Communications Leadership Award, Advertising Council Forty-Third Annual Washington Conference Awards Dinner, Westin Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1987 May 20 (Box 27)
  - "Changing Role of Police Officer," comments, Police Executive Research Forum 9th Annual Meeting, Ramada Renaissance Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1987 May 20 (Box 27)
  - Address, American Law Institute Luncheon, Mayflower Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1987 May 22 (Box 27)
  - "The American Focus," comments on civil rights policy, WPGC - FM radio, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1987 May 24 (Box 27)
  - Speech, farewell ceremony for William Webster, Washington, D.C., 1987 May 27 (Box 27)
  - Address, Council for National Policy Dinner, Dallas, Texas, 1987 May 29 (Box 27)
  - Commencement address, New England School of Law, Boston, Massachusetts, 1987 May 29 (Box 27)
  - Speech, Federal Bureau of Investigation National Executive Institute and IACP Seminar, Sun Valley, Idaho, 1987 June 3 (Box 28)
  - Address, Civil Affairs Association 40th Annual Conference Banquet, Capitol Hilton Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1987 June 6 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Victim - Witness - LECC Coordinators, Washington, D.C., 1987 June 8 (Box 28)
  - Remarks, National Association of Attorneys General, Coeur d'Alene, Idaho, 1987 June 9 (Box 28)
  - Speech, State Department Briefing for U.S. Delegation to Vienna Drug Conference, Loy Henderson auditorium, Vienna, Virginia, 1987 June 11 (Box 28)
  - Address, American Studies Center Bicentennial Program Luncheon, Mayflower Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1987 June 12 (Box 28)
  - Speech, National Institute of Justice 3rd National Conference on "Policing," Phoenix, Arizona, 1987 June 12 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Federal Bureau of Investigation National Academy 149th Graduation, Quantico, Virginia, 1987 June 12 (Box 28)
  - Address, National Institute of Justice 3rd National Conference on Policing Breakfast, Phoenix, Arizona, 1987 June 13 (Box 28)
  - Remarks, International Conference on Drug Abuse and Illicit Trafficking, Vienna, Austria, 1987 June 17 (Box 28)
  - Interview re: drugs, Today Show, Vienna, Austria, 1987 June 18 (Box 28)
  - Address, International Association of Chiefs of Police, Hamburg, Germany, 1987 June 24 (Box 28)
  - Press conference, Hamburg, Germany, 1987 June 24 (Box 28)
  - Press conference, Chautauqua Institute, Chautauqua, New York, 1987 June 29 (Box 28)
  - Remarks, Chautauqua Institute Conference on the American Constitution, Chautauqua, New York, 1987 June 29 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Bureau of Prisons retirement dinner for Norm Carlson, Arlington, Virginia, 1987 June 30 (Box 28)
  - Address, National Association of Student Councils, Williamsville High School, Buffalo, New York, 1987 July 2 (Box 28)
  - Remarks, Buffalo Chamber of Commerce and Friendship Festival, Buffalo, New York, 1987 July 2 (Box 28)
  - Press conference, Convention Center, Buffalo, New York, 1987 July 2 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Editorial Review Board, Buffalo, New York, 1987 July 2 (Box 28)
  - Remarks, First Lady's Drug Abuse Policy Briefing, Indian Treaty Room, White House, Washington, D.C., 1987 July 22 (Box 28)
  - Address to Department of Justice Summer Law Interns, Great Hall, Department of Justice, Washington, D.C., 1987 July 23 (Box 28)
  - Statement, United States Senate Select Committee on Secret Military Assistance to Iran and the Nicaraguan Opposition (and the United States House of Representatives Select Committee), Washington, D.C., 1987 July 28 (Box 28)
  - Remarks, Special Olympics Conference, Soldier's Field, Chicago, Illinois, 1987 July 30 (Box 28)
  - Press conference re: drug bust, Chicago, Illinois, 1987 July 30 (Box 29)
  - Interview, CBS Morning News, Washington, D.C., 1987 July 30 (Box 29)
  - Guest appearance, Today Show, NBC Network, Washington, D.C., 1987 July 30 (Box 29)
  - Interview, Good Morning America, ABC - TV, Washington, D.C., 1987 July 30 (Box 29)
  - Address, Tenth Judicial Circuit Annual Conference, San Diego, California, 1987 July 31 (Box 29)
  - Guest appearance, Evans and Novak, Cable News Network, Chicago, Illinois, 1987 August 1 (Box 29)
  - Interview, This Week with David Brinkley, ABC Network, Washington, D.C., 1987 August 2 (Box 29)
  - Remarks, Junior Statesmen Foundation Summer School Briefing, White House, Washington, D.C., 1987 August 4 (Box 29)
  - Address, National Association of Police Organizations 9th Annual Convention, Plymouth, Massachusetts, 1987 August 7 (Box 29)
  - Speech, American Bar Association House of Delegates, San Francisco, California, 1987 August 11 (Box 29)
  - Address, American Bar Association Criminal Justice Section, San Francisco, California, 1987 August 11 (Box 29)
  - Address, U.S.-China Joint Session on Trade, Investment and Economic Law, Great Hall of the People, Beijing, China, 1987 August 17 (Box 29)
  - Closing remarks, U.S.-China Joint Session on Trade, Investment and Economic Law, Great Hall of the People, Beijing, China, 1987 August 19 (Box 29)
  - Speech, Ninth Circuit Judicial Conference, Hawaii, 1987 August 21 (Box 29)
  - Address, Hawaii Loa College, Kaneohe, Hawaii, 1987 August 25 (Box 29)
  - Special interview for the student body, Hawaii Loa College, Kaneohe, Hawaii, 1987 August 25 (Box 29)
  - Address, Hawaii State Law Enforcement Officers Association, Kauai, Hawaii, 1987 August 27 (Box 29)
  - "How Does the Constitution Establish Justice?," speech, Department of Justice and the American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, Capitol Hilton Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1987 September 11-12 (Box 29)
  - Opening remarks, American Enterprise Institute and Department of Justice Bicentennial Conference, Capitol Hilton Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1987 September 11 (Box 30)
  - Speech, Immigration and Naturalization Service Four-Country Conference, conference room, Department of Justice, Washington, D.C., 1987 September 14 (Box 30)
  - Address, Community Relations Service National Conference, Hunt Valley, Maryland, 1987 September 15 (Box 30)
  - Remarks, Hispanic Heritage Week Celebration, Great Hall, Department of Justice, Washington, D.C., 1987 September 16 (Box 30)
  - Address, Reserve Forces Policy Board Breakfast, Pentagon, Washington, D.C., 1987 September 16 (Box 30)
  - Speech, Third Circuit Judicial Conference, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1987 September 18 (Box 30)
  - Remarks, Congress on the Bible II, D.C. Convention Center, Washington, D.C, 1987 September 23 (Box 30)
  - Address, Immigration and Naturalization Service Fourth Annual Conference, Fair Oaks Holiday Inn, Fairfax, Virginia, 1987 September 24 (Box 30)
  - Speech, National Black Republican Council, Washington Plaza Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1987 September 24 (Box 30)
  - Remarks, Constitution Day Ceremonies, San Diego, California, 1987 September 26 (Box 30)
  - Address, California-Nevada-Hawaii District Lutheran Church Celebration, Lodi, California, 1987 September 26 (Box 30)
  - Speech, National Guard Association 109th Annual Conference, Portland, Oregon, 1987 September 28 (Box 30)
  - Remarks, Business Council, Hot Springs, Virginia, 1987 October 9 (Box 31)
  - Address, Free Masons of California Breakfast, San Francisco, California, 1987 October 14 (Box 31)
  - Remarks, United States Customs Service, Washington, D.C., 1987 October 16 (Box 31)
  - Speech, Junior Statesmen Foundation Luncheon, Capitol Hill, Washington, D.C., 1987 October 19 (Box 31)
  - Address, National War College, Washington, D.C., 1987 October 19 (Box 31)
  - Address, American Stock Exchange Conference, Washington, D.C., 1987 October 19 (Box 31)
  - Remarks, National Guard Bureau 17th Annual Dining-In, Andrews Air Force Base, Maryland, 1987 October 30 (Box 31)
  - Speech, U.S. Chamber of Commerce Association "Insiders" Breakfast, Washington, D.C., 1987 October 30 (Box 31)
  - Address, Morality in the Media 4th National Conference, Orlando, Florida, 1987 October 31 (Box 31)
  - Speech, Citizens for America Salute to the Constitution, Sarasota, Florida, 1987 November 1 (Box 31)
  - Remarks, U.S.-Nigeria Mutual Assistance in Law Enforcement Matters Signing Ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1987 November 2 (Box 31)
  - Remarks, swearing-in of Judge William S. Sessions, FBI Courtyard, Washington, D.C., 1987 November 2 (Box 31)
  - Address, White House Conference on a Drug-Free America, Omaha, Nebraska, 1987 November 2 (Box 31)
  - Remarks, White House Conference on Drugs, Omaha, Nebraska, 1987 November 3-4 (Box 31)
  - Comments, Fourth Annual Regan-Bush Reunion, Washington, D.C., 1987 November 4 (Box 31)
  - Remarks, Victims of Crime Ceremony, White House, Washington, D.C., 1987 November 5 (Box 31)
  - Address, Federalist Society, Washington, D.C., 1987 November 7 (Box 31)
  - Speech, Federal Bureau of Investigation Hall of Honor Dedication Ceremony, FBI National Academy, Quantico, Virginia, 1987 November 10 (Box 31)
  - Address, Center for the Study of the Presidency, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1987 November 14 (Box 31)
  - Remarks, Institute for the Study of Conflict, Washington, D.C., 1987 November 17 (Box 31)
  - Speech, Junior Statesmen Foundation Dinner, Georgetown Club, Washington, D.C., 1987 November 19 (Box 31)
  - Address, Law Enforcement Assistance Foundation, New York, 1987 November 19 (Box 32)
  - Speech, American Bar Association Standing Committee on Law and National Security Breakfast, Washington, D.C., 1987 November 19 (Box 32)
  - Remarks, Intercollegiate Studies Institute Bicentennial Celebration, Villanova University, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1987 November 20 (Box 32)
  - Opening remarks, Department of Justice Tort Reform Symposium, Hyatt Arlington Hotel, Arlington, Virginia, 1987 November 21 (Box 32)
  - Remarks, National Law Enforcement Officers Memorial Fund Reception, Washington, D.C., 1987 November 23 (Box 32)
  - Speech, Association of Federal Investigators, Washington, D.C., 1987 December 2 (Box 32)
  - Address, American Conservative Union "Support Edwin Meese Rally," NG building, Washington, D.C., 1987 December 3 (Box 32)
  - Speech, Heritage Foundation Business Executives, Washington, D.C., 1987 December 4 (Box 32)
  - Address, Attorney General's 36th Annual Awards Ceremony, Great Hall, Department of Justice, Washington, D.C., 1987 December 4 (Box 32)
  - Speech, National Association of Attorneys General, San Diego, California, 1987 December 12 (Box 32)
  - Remarks and press conference, Immigration and Naturalization Service, San Francisco, California, 1987 December 14 (Box 32)
  - Press conference, 3rd Annual Meeting with Attorney General of Mexico and Attorneys General of Border States, Victoria, Mexico, 1987 December 15 (Box 32)
  - Speech, 3rd Annual Border Conference, Victoria, Mexico, 1987 December 15 (Box 32)
  - Press conference, Iran/Contra affair, Washington, D.C., 1987 December (Box 32)
  - Address, American Correctional Association, Phoenix, Arizona, 1988 January 12 (Box 32)
  - Address, Virginia Bar Association, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1988 January 15 (Box 32)
  - Remarks, Martin Luther King Day Program, Great Hall, Department of Justice, Washington, D.C., 1988 January 15 (Box 33)
  - Press conference, Oakdale Prison, Oakdale, Louisiana, 1988 January 15 (Box 33)
  - Press conference re: Drug Use Forecasting Program, Washington, D.C., 1988 January 21 (Box 33)
  - Speech, Students for America Luncheon Award, Crystal City, Virginia, 1988 January 31 (Box 33)
  - Address, Lawyers for the Republic, Washington, D.C., 1988 February 18 (Box 33)
  - Opening remarks, OJP: Coordinating Council on Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Prevention, Attorney General conference room, Department of Justice, Washington, D.C., 1988 February 18 (Box 33)
  - Address, United States Attorneys Conference, San Diego, California, 1988 February 20 (Box 33)
  - Speech, Immigration and Naturalization Service, San Diego, California, 1988 February 22 (Box 33)
  - Remarks, Law Enforcement Coordinating Council, Birmingham, Alabama, 1988 February 29 (Box 33)
  - Press conference, Birmingham, Alabama, 1988 February 29 (Box 33)
  - Remarks, Governor's Conference on Drug Awareness, Birmingham, Alabama, 1988 February 29 (Box 33)
  - Address, Cumberland School of Law, Samford University, Birmingham, Alabama, 1988 February 29 (Box 33)
  - Speech, White House Conference for a Drug-Free America, Omni Shoreham Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1988 March 2 (Box 33)
  - Meese and Drugs, interview, "Good Morning America," ABC - TV, Washington, D.C., 1988 March 3 (Box 33)
  - Remarks, Media Executives Drug Abuse Briefing, Indian Treaty Room, White House, Washington, D.C., 1988 March 7 (Box 33)
  - Guest opinion, Philadelphia Daily News, 1988 March 9 (Box 33)
  - Guest appearance, This Week with David Brinkley, ABC Network, Washington, D.C., 1988 March 13 (Box 33)
  - Address, Yale Political Students Union, Washington, D.C., 1988 March 15 (Box 33)
  - Statement, House Appropriations Subcommittee on the Departments on Commerce, Justice, and State, the Judiciary, and Related Agencies, Washington, D.C., 1988 March 16 (Box 33)
  - Interview re: drugs, New York Times, Washington, D.C., 1988 March 17 (Box 33)
  - Address to Houston High School Interns, Washington, D.C., 1988 March 17 (Box 33)
  - Press conference, Immigration and Naturalization Service, Arlington, Virginia, 1988 March 18 (Box 33)
  - Remarks, Counsel of Independent Regulatory Agencies, Washington, D.C., 1988 March 18 (Box 33)
  - Address, American Business Conference, Sheraton Grand Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1988 March 22 (Box 33)
  - Speech, Joseph Story Society Awards Banquet honoring Robert Bork and Raoul Berger, Mayflower Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1988 March 24 (Box 34)
  - Remarks, National Youth Leaders Conference, National Press Club, Washington, D.C., 1988 March 29 (Box 34)
  - Interview with Barbara Walters, 20/20, ABC - TV, Attorney General's conference room, Washington, D.C., 1988 April 1 (Box 34)
  - Speech, Senior Executive Service, Capitol Hilton Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1988 April 4 (Box 34)
  - Public Service Announcement (radio) re: immigration legalization, Washington, D.C., 1988 April 5 (Box 34)
  - Address, National Pride Convention, Atlanta, Georgia, 1988 April 14 (Box 34)
  - Remarks, Drug Enforcement Agency memorial service honoring public servants slain in the struggle against drugs, Rose Garden, White House, Washington, D.C., 1988 April 19 (Box 34)
  - Statement, US Senate Appropriations Committee, Washington, D.C., 1988 April 20 (Box 34)
  - Interview, USA Today, 1988 April 21 (Box 34)
  - Press conference, Immigration and Naturalization Service, Detroit, Michigan, 1988 April 25 (Box 34)
  - Remarks, Detroit Economic Club, Detroit, Michigan, 1988 April 25 (Box 34)
  - Speech, U.S. Conference of Mayors and Police Policy Board, Hyatt Regency Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1988 April 26 (Box 34)
  - Speech, Kiwanis Club Annual Law Day Luncheon, Washington, D.C., 1988 April 28 (Box 34)
  - Address, Heritage Foundation National Issues Series for Business Executives Forum, Heritage Foundation, Washington, D.C., 1988 April 29 (Box 34)
  - British TV interview with Godfrey Hodgson, Washington, D.C., 1988 April 29 (Box 34)
  - Remarks to White House Fellows Alumni, Capitol Hilton Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1988 May 7 (Box 35)
  - Address, Law Enforcement Coordinating Council - Victim Witness Coordinators' National Training Conference Luncheon, National Clarion Hotel, Arlington, Virginia, 1988 May 10 (Box 35)
  - Interview with Michael Hedges, Washington Times, 1988 May 11 (Box 35)
  - Address, National Troopers Annual Spring Conference, National Clarion Hotel, Arlington, Virginia, 1988 May 12 (Box 35)
  - Speech, Asian Pacific Heritage Ceremony, courtyard, Department of Justice, Washington, D.C., 1988 May 12 (Box 35)
  - Address, U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit 6th Annual Judicial Conference, Washington, D.C., 1988 May 13 (Box 35)
  - Remarks, National Law Enforcement Officers memorial service, Ellipse, Washington, D.C., 1988 May 15 (Box 35)
  - Press conference, National Law Enforcement Officers memorial service, Ellipse, Washington, D.C., 1988 May 15 (Box 35)
  - Remarks, Drug-Free Schools Awards Ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1988 May 16 (Box 35)
  - Presentation, Voice of America Workshop, Washington, D.C., 1988 May 16 (Box 35)
  - Address, Police Executive Research Forum, Ramada Renaissance Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1988 May 18 (Box 35)
  - Speech, Department of Justice Criminal Justice Conference, Madison Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1988 May 20 (Box 35)
  - Brief remarks as Honorary Chairman, D.C. Special Olympics Third Annual Law Enforcement Torch Run, U.S. Capitol, Washington, D.C., 1988 May 20 (Box 35)
  - Remarks, S.A.C. Conference, Federal Bureau of Investigation, Palm Beach, Florida, 1988 May 23 (Box 35)
  - Address, Advanced Obscenity and Child Pornography Conference for Assistant U.S. Attorneys, National Clarion Hotel, Arlington, Virginia, 1988 May 25 (Box 35)
  - Speech, Takings and Executive Order 12630 Program, National Archives, Washington, D.C., 1988 May 25 (Box 35)
  - Interview, Larry King Show, Washington, D.C., 1988 May 30 (Box 35)
  - Address, Federal Bureau of Investigation National Executive Institute Speech and Press Conference, Sun Valley, Idaho, 1988 June 6 (Box 35)
  - Greetings to the American Inns of Court Fourth Annual Meeting, Madison Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1988 June 10 (Box 35)
  - Remarks, Cuban Refugee Program Signing Ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1988 June 13 (Box 35)
  - Address, Drug Enforcement Administration memorial service, Fort McNair, Washington, D.C., 1988 June 20 (Box 35)
  - Opening remarks, International Homicide Symposium, Quantico, Virginia, 1988 June 20 (Box 36)
  - Press interview, National Association of Attorneys General, Hilton Head, South Carolina, 1988 June 21 (Box 36)
  - Remarks, National Association of Attorneys General Summer Meeting, Hilton Head, South Carolina, 1988 June 21 (Box 36)
  - Remarks, U.S. Court of Appeals and U.S. District Court Law Clerks Luncheon, U.S. courthouse, Washington, D.C., 1988 June 23 (Box 36)
  - Address, Heritage Foundation National Issues Series for Business Executives Forum, Heritage Foundation, Washington, D.C., 1988 June 23 (Box 36)
  - Speech, Presidential Classroom, Omni Shoreham Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1988 June 24 (Box 36)